<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>OliverWEB 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <language>en</language>
      <copyright>Copyright 2006</copyright>
      <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 18:22:39 -0600</lastBuildDate>
      <generator>http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/?v=3.2</generator>
      <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 

            <item>
         <title>Sunscreen Tattoos</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Okay, I felt kinda weird taking these (and posting them), haha, but I'll do it anyways for all of you to admire my hot bod. ;)  So at the beach in Florida, Megan and Kathy drew stuff on me with sunscreen and this is how it turned out:</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/231376706/" title="Photo Sharing"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/83/231376706_80e509267e.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="<3" /></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/231377854/" title="Photo Sharing"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/76/231377854_5c6b728621.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="MOM" /></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/231374395/" title="Photo Sharing"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/73/231374395_8cd0c49e76.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="=)" /></a></p>

<p>I showed some coworkers the smiley and they laughed and asked if I was asleep when people drew on me, haha... then were kinda skeptical I voluntarily let this happen... =)</p>

<p><i>"Ugly Day the sun is shining, <br />
Every cloud's got a silver lining. <br />
Ugly day the skies are blue, <br />
Now every day is ugly without you."</i> - Five Iron Frenzy</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/09/sunscreen_tatto.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/09/sunscreen_tatto.php</guid>
         <category>photographs</category>
         <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 18:22:39 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Yay!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Went running yesterday with Kathy and Olivia, and this time successfully did not lose Olivia, haha.  I also got really hungry yesterday for some reason and after eating dinner, I ate a turkey leg, chunks of cheese, an apple and other random stuff.  I think this running thing is making my metabolism go crazy... speaking of which, who wants to do <a href="http://www.hairymanfestival.org/5k.html">the Hairy Man 5k</a>? Haha...</p>

<p>*gack*  I just accidently swallowed my Starburst whole... oh... this is not a pleasant feeling... at all...</p>

<p>My work desk is covered with lots of boxes, wires going everywhere, LCD displays, and development boards.  Some coworkers that I make snack runs with made comments on how messy my desk was, so I cleaned it up a bit, haha.  It was becoming a problem when getting to my phone was difficult...</p>

<p>The new OliverWEB layout is getting there, but it still seems like it's missing a little bit... I'm not sure what it is yet.  I'll probably convert it to CSS/HTML soon and play around with it there a bit.  Going to use <a href="http://www.owiber.com">owiber.com</a> as my development location for now since I'm switching over to WordPress too.  Hip! Hip! HORAY!</p>

<p><i>"As I walk this land with broken dreams<br />
I have visions of many things<br />
Love's happiness is just an illusion<br />
Filled with sadness and confusion,<br />
What becomes of the broken hearted<br />
Who had love that's now departed?<br />
I know I've got to find<br />
Some kind of peace of mind"</i> - Jimmy Ruffin</p>

<p>Haha, all these lyrics read so much sadder than they sound (in the song)...</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/09/yay.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/09/yay.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 13:25:07 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Pink!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>I know Andrew loves my love for pink.  So this change is dedicated to him. =)  Don't worry, entirely new layout (not comprising pink) is due in a month-ish...</p>

<p><i>"(Ooh love Ooh lover boy)<br />
What ya doin' tonight, (hey boy)<br />
Set my alarm, turn on my charm<br />
That's because I'm a good old fashioned lover boy"</i> - Queen</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/pink.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/pink.php</guid>
         <category>events</category>
         <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 01:25:53 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>UT</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Have a good semester/year, peeps. =)</p>

<p>Was around campus a few times the past week or two and it made me start to miss it a lot.  Poo.  Maybe it won't be so bad once everyone I know there has graduated, but I liked walking around campus with the swarms of people everywhere.  I think what I miss the most is random campus meets like lunches, late night snacks, and all that stuff.  It is nice to never have to worry about homework and tests now though and I have more money, haha... </p>

<p>I've got one idea for <a href="http://www.owiber.com">owiber.com</a>, but I'm not sure if it will conflict too much with OliverWEB... I may not be able to keep both updated concurrently... so we'll see.</p>

<p>So I've been considering running around Town Lake without a shirt so that I don't get an absurd farmer's tan... but right now, I currently have a very visible heart on my chest which is making me hesitate a bit... lol.</p>

<p>Edit: Forgot lyrics. =)</p>

<p><i>"Here's my story, its sad but true<br />
It's about a girl that I once knew<br />
She took my love then ran around<br />
With every single guy in town"</i> - Dion</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/ut.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/ut.php</guid>
         <category>events</category>
         <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 09:38:28 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Owiber</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>So yesterday I went on an 'owiber' registration spree and registered owiber@gmail.com and owiber.com.  I tried to make an owiber Blogger account, but apparently I <a href="http://owiber.blogspot.com/">already had one</a>, so I just made a post instead.  Doing a Google search for <a href="http://www.google.com/search?q=owiber">owiber</a> reveals a lot of accounts I wasn't aware or didn't remember I had, haha...</p>

<p>Now I'm not sure what to do with owiber.com.  I could just make it point to OliverWEB as well, but I was thinking something else would be more fun... <i>but what?</i> =)</p>

<p><i>"Crooked souls trying to stay up straight<br />
Dry eyes in the pouring rain well<br />
The shadow proves the sunshine"</i> - Switchfoot</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/owiber.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/owiber.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2006 17:06:15 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Mountain of Glooooooom</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>I don't know if it's just the weather, the having to go back to work after a great vacation, the missing school-feeling or what, but I felt rather gloomy today.  When I run, I set landmarks for myself that I force myself to hit.  "Just get to the next bridge" or something more important like "just make it to land, so you don't drown."  I guess I felt like that today... "just get through the meeting" or "just finish up _______ for _______ and before you know it, you'll get to go home."</p>

<p>I really feel like running... in the rain, unfortunately, the rain's probably over now, eh?  Oh well, at least the sun's heat is somewhat deflected by the clouds... <i>but not the UV rays, kids!</i></p>

<p><i>"You had a bad day <br />
You're taking one down <br />
You sing a sad song just to turn it around <br />
You say you don't know <br />
You tell me don't lie <br />
You work at a smile and you go for a ride"</i> - Daniel Powter</p>

<p>lol... posting that makes me feel like a fruity emo kid...</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/mountain_of_glo.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/mountain_of_glo.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2006 16:32:44 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Poo</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>I don't want to go back to work.  More vacation, please. =(</p>

<p>"<i>And if he falls in love tonight,<br />
It can be assumed<br />
His carefree days with us are history.<br />
In short, our pal is doomed.</i>" - Timon & Pumbaa (The Lion King)</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/poo.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/poo.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 23:24:40 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Florida - Day 3 + 4</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, we went to church and then did a bunch of nothing to recooperate from the Busch Gardens and beach trips the prior two days.  Had nice mid-day naps. Yaaaay!  Then we watched The New World, which was a horrible waste of time and Flightplan, which was less so.</p>

<p>I don't even really know if I have any pictures or videos from yesterday worth mentioning... I might scrounge up the flash cards and see later though.  Speaking of which, I uploaded <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/sets/72157594253941893/">pictures from Busch Gardens</a> yesterday.</p>

<p>Anyways, back in Austin now and I am ready to take a long nap.  Thanks to Andrew, Jen, and all the other Floridians that hung out with us while we were there, had a great time!</p>

<p><i>"And Leonard Nemoy<br />
can't stand up to this.<br />
And Captain James T. Kirk<br />
bows beneath my fists!<br />
And I am awesome!<br />
Awesome!<br />
I am the awesomest!"</i> - Five Iron Frenzy</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_3_4.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_3_4.php</guid>
         <category>events</category>
         <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 13:36:37 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Florida - Day 2</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Today we went to some beach four hours away and woke up really early to do so.  Was quite a bit of fun, but I think all of us (except for Andrew) got burnt.  I did, however, put a small amount of sunscreen on myself (or rather, other people put it on me) to make a heart on my chest, a smiley on my right arm and "MOM" on my left arm.  The heart didn't turn out so well, I think, but Van <i>might</i> have a decent picture.</p>

<p>I'm going to be uploading pics to my <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber">flickr</a> as I sleep, I'll title them later... heh... Edit: Ok, never mind, I titled them already. =)  And here's a pic just for our favorite Brit:</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/225840458/" title="Photo Sharing"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/73/225840458_eb82d6f165.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="For VJ" /></a></p>

<p>We finished the night off watching True Lies at Jen's again... wheeeee!</p>

<p>And, this song is a throat killer:</p>

<p><i>"If I should stay,<br />
I would only be in your way.<br />
So I'll go <br />
But I know <br />
I'll think of you every step of the way.</p>

<p>And I will always love you<br />
Will always love you."</i> - Whitney Houston</p>

<p>That song always reminds me of Kevin Costner...</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_2.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_2.php</guid>
         <category>events</category>
         <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2006 01:06:14 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Florida - Day 1</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>So Day 1 in Florida (not counting the day we arrived) was spent at Busch Gardens.  In the following video, you can see Andrew, Van and I slightly confused as far as amusement parks go... (Floridians will probably not understand this):</p>

<p><object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/TzxZoIimimM"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/TzxZoIimimM" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="350"></embed></object></p>

<p>We also rode ultra-exciting rides like the following log ride (feel free to stop watching after a minute or so... it gets boring after that, haha):</p>

<p><object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/BtQgOhzZlVM"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/BtQgOhzZlVM" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="350"></embed></object></p>

<p>Haha... actually, it was pretty fun (and the coasters were more lively than the above =)... Kathy even went on some! ...and got really nasty wrinkled feet from getting socks/shoes soaked... ewww... but she wouldn't let me take a picture of them.</p>

<p>Afterwards, we went back to Jen's place and watched Four Brothers... better than I expected it to be, actually, haha.</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_1.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/florida_day_1.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2006 23:12:47 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>We&apos;re Off!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>...well, soon anyways.  See ya, Texas!</p>

<p><i>"So kiss me and smile for me<br />
Tell me that you'll wait for me<br />
Hold me like you'll never let me go<br />
cause I'm leavin on a jet plane<br />
Don't know when I'll be back again<br />
Oh babe, I hate to go"</i> - John Denver</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/were_off.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/were_off.php</guid>
         <category>events</category>
         <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 14:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Oink - 50mm f/1.4</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/223206903/" title="Oink"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/58/223206903_4976653f4a.jpg" alt="Oink" /></a><br />
<br />Took this shot with my new 50mm f/1.4.  I think I'm gonna try it out for a bit and maybe sell off my 85L.  I don't think I'll even bring my 85L to Florida... well, maybe I will... hmm, we'll see... I must pack...<br /><br />
I've been making a decent amount of OliverWEB drafts, but haven't come up with a design I want to stick with yet.  Well, I've got a month and so to come up with something, so we'll see. =)<br /><br />
I kind of want to use pink in the new layout, but not too much cause it'll just contrast too much with pictures I post, I think. Haha... maybe a splash... =)</p>

<p><i>"Poor unfortunate souls!<br />
In pain.<br />
In need. <br />
This one longing to be thinner.<br />
That one wants to get the girl.<br />
And do I help them? <br />
Yes, indeed."</i> - Ursula  (The Little Mermaid)</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/oink_50mm_f14.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/oink_50mm_f14.php</guid>
         <category>photographs</category>
         <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2006 23:54:06 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Messages</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/owiber/222633689/" title="Message for Roommates"><img src="http://static.flickr.com/84/222633689_c0cf1c1607.jpg" alt="Message for Roommates" /></a><br />
<br />I like leaving messages for my roomies.  Sometimes they're nice, sometime's they're not. =)</p>

<p>On an entirely unrelated note, I tried the "shortcut swim" again, but this time giving Kathy my shoes before doing so and it went oh so much better, haha...</p>

<p><i>"Beautiful day,<br />
wonderful feeling,<br />
I feel like singing,<br />
psalms meaning songs singing praises all day long.<br />
Joy fills the weak,<br />
joy makes us strong.<br />
Filled 'till we burst,<br />
songs of praise to the God of the Universe."</i> - Five Iron Frenzy</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/messages.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/messages.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2006 02:54:18 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Hey!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>You guys need to blog more, I can't keep the blog count up for everyone here.  What am I supposed to do when I'm waiting for a kernel to finish compiling, huh?</p>

<p>I was thinking of cool things to do in Florida and somehow thought it would be funny to bring a bag full of LEGOs to the beach, but decided that was probably a bad idea (I'm sure you can come up with quite a few reasons why).  Then, I thought it'd be cool to bring that bag on the airplane to build something cool on the flight, but realized I would probably drive everyone around me insane with all the LEGO shuffling, haha.</p>

<p>So I think I like the 50mm on the 5D a lot better than the 85mm.  I think the 85mm still seems a bit too "tight" for me for everything except solo portrait shots (which it does insanely well with... oh the bokeh...).  I bought a 50mm f/1.4 which should hopefully arrive before the Florida trip.  Highly considering selling the 85L, if my run with the 50mm f/1.4 goes well.  I know it won't be nearly as sharp... but since I already have the 85 f/1.8 (which is nearly just as sharp as the 85 f/1.2, just can't stop down as low and doesn't have <i>as</i> nice bokeh), I'm not sure if I use the 85L enough to justify keeping it...</p>

<p><i>"halogen, the lights will flicker <br />
incadescent burning lies <br />
and the silence stands for nothing <br />
desperate, I search the skies aching for a spark <br />
trembling in pitchest dark"</i> - Brave Saint Saturn</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/hey.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/hey.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 16:12:23 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
            <item>
         <title>Yay Concierge!</title>
         <description><![CDATA[<p>Freescale has a concierge service (which I think they contract from another company or something) which I've found useful on a few occasions.  Today, I had the guy take my car to get an oil change. Wheeee!</p>

<p>Although, I just realized that since I'm taking tomorrow off, I could have done it then.  Oh well, more time to <i>relaaaaax</i>. =)</p>

<p>Uh oh, meeting time...</p>

<p><i>"When the toast is burning<br />
And all the milk has turned<br />
And Captain Crunch is waving farewell<br />
When the big one finds you<br />
May this song remind you<br />
That they don't serve breakfast in hell"</i> - Newsboys</p>]]></description>
         <link>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/yay_concierge.php</link>
         <guid>http://www.oliverweb.com/archives/2006/08/yay_concierge.php</guid>
         <category>misc</category>
         <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 12:19:01 -0600</pubDate>
      </item>
      
   </channel>
</rss>
